小学的时候我们都是洛伦佐老师班上的
l Iiked you back When We Was in elementarym
那时候我就喜欢上你了
in I\/lr. LorenZo's class.
但是我也很喜欢你
l liked you, too.
我希望我能早点知道
Wish l kneW that.
不过我当时那么皮 想必我们也走不到一起
Though l Would've needed an instruction manual back then.
你有想过要做点几别的吗
Ever thought about doing something else?
换个另外的工作什么的?
Some other kind of Work?
也没什么正经工作可找
Not real serious or anything.
我在超市干过一段时间
Worked at the mall for a little While.
让我再看看你吧
Let me lo0k if you don't mind.
我有好长时间没有看过女人的身体了
I've had a Iong intermission.
我周二要找安德烈谈一谈
l'mma talk With Andre on Tuesday.
如果有空缺的职位你会感兴趣吗
You interested if something comes up?
我想先适应一下
Before I consider that kind of vocation,
再开始找工作
l need to get myself acclimated.
我理解
Certainly.
四处走走 呼吸一些新鲜空气 凝望蓝天
Walk around, breathe some air, gaze at the sky,
看看铁门外的天空有多蓝
see hoW blue it Iooks on the outside.
好好享受 出狱生活
Enjoy yourself.
我安顿好后 会马上告诉你的
Once I've settled, l'Il Iet you knoW.
总之
Anyhowm
谢谢你帮我联系了拉娜
thanks for setting that up With Lana.
也谢谢你接我回来
And for fetching.
不客气
Certainly.
回见
See you.
嗯 啊
Um, uhm
宝贝 先回你自己的房间好吗
Babx go back to your rooln okay?
-妈妈现在很忙 一我不是伊森
- Mamak busy - This ain't Ethan.
亨瑞
Heng/?
对头
Yeah.
-快把衣服穿好 -听着
- Get some clothes onm - Loolcn
我现在在忙
/ got company r/ght nom LH
把衣服穿上 叫那个混蛋滚
Put some clothes on and eject that nigga
不然我就拿他脑袋练全垒打
or I'm practicing home runs on his sku‖.
动作快点
Move Iike you in fast-forWard.
你没权利到这里来
Loolç you am 't got no r/g/7t c0m/hg hera
我拿着棒球棍 这扇门几杆子就能被我打穿
That Was a baseball bat and this door's beyond flimsy.
好吧 好吧
Okax okây
至少先让我们把衣服穿好啊 倒了血霉了
Let us get ourselves dressed Damn.
我正在赶他出来
Forcing my friend out.
你得保证 你不能伤害他
You gotta promise you're not gonna hurt him.
滚
Out.
再敢约我妈 我就宰了你
Ca‖ my mother again and l'll crack your sku‖.
- 懂么? -懂
- Understand? - I do.
很好
'Aight.
把门外的垃圾袋提到楼下垃圾桶里
Take those garbage bags that are outside doWn to the trash.
好的
Okay, l Wi‖.
笨蛋 你刚刚搅黄了我的生意
Fool, you just cost me.
妈 你干这个多久了
Ma, hoW long you been doing this?
没多久
Not Iong.
你在杂货店的工作呢
What happened to yourjob at the grocery?
我被开除了
lgot fired.
我进监狱之前不是给你留了钱吗
l Ieft you money before I Went in.
就算我进去两次号 也完全够用啊
PIenty for tWice as long.
用完了啊
lt ran out.
好吧
Yeahm
看你手臂上的针孔 我算是明白钱用哪儿去了
And l can see its footprints up and doWn your arms.
听好了 你没权利教育我
Look, you ain't got no right Iecturing me about nothing.
进监狱的是你 我只是被逼无奈
Your ass Went tojail. l did What l had to do.
妈 咱们不说这些了
Ma, Iet's fast-forWard all this.
一直讨论过去的事几也没有意义
Ain't no point in arguing about a bunch of yesterdays.
你不能再这样 了
You can't be doing this.
卖身 吸毒
Hooking, needlesm
特别是当着伊森的面 你更不能这么做
and especially not in front of Ethan at all ever.
他又不是小孩了
He ain't a toddler no m0re.
你在他身边做这些事
And you doing those things around him,
会害他一辈子的
it'‖ mess him up permanent
你现在想起来管我们 了?
So, you gonna take care of us noW, huh?
你那个见屌眼看的老爸
Like your cocl<-sucking father did
和他的小基佬一起携屌潜逃时 你怎么不说话?
When he ran off With his faggot-ass boyfriend?
我爸只是不值一提的往事
Pops is a yesterday Who ain't Worth Words.
难道你一 出狱就能找到工作?
You got opportunities ríght out the penitentiary?
有可能
l might.
我们家的房租 账单己经拖欠了6个月了
Look, We are siX months behind on bi‖s, rent, everything.
追债的就像苍蝇一样 无处不在
And the collection agency, they buzzing like mosquitoesm
我知道了
'Aight.
好好照顾自己 还有这个家
Start organizing yourself and this placem
其他的事 我会想办法的
and l'Il figure things.
伊森回来了吗
Ethan home?
干嘛
Whafi
是我
It's me.
亨利
Hen/y?
- 你哪天出来的 - 今天
- When 'dy0u get out of the oven? - Today.
我能进来吗
Can l come in?
可以
Yeahm
妈妈叫我把门锁好
Mom told me to /0c/( the door
因为晚点会有陌生男人来家里
'cause a man was c0m/hg over laten
我马上来
/777 c0m/ng.
听起来你的轮椅需要加些润滑油 了
Sounds Iike you could use some oil.
妈 你有吗 味道好闻点的那种
Ma, you got any? Some kind that smells good.
我有那种带软木塞的意大利货
I got the italian kind with the cork in it
可以
That'‖ Work.
长了不少肌肉嘛
Lo0ks Iike you've been Working out.
嗯 我有举哑铃
Yeah, l've been doing curls.
要做就做一整套的
Let's do it proper.
给我看看你在信里面提到的
So, you Wanna shoW me those Vídeo games
那些游戏好吗?
you talked about in your letters?
你要住在这儿吗
Are you gonna stay here?
是的
lamm
直到一切都回归正轨为止
till things are sort of correct.
三周后
我的呢
Where's mine?
洒了
Spi‖ed.
你没想过回去再给我买一杯吗
You didn't think to go back and get me another?
我们不是还在执行任务嘛
Accelerated the event.
时间紧任务重
There Was Iittle time and less inclination.
抠门
Prick.
我以为告诉你 我只买了自己的...
l thought you'd be okay Withm
你不会生气呢
mejust telling you about mine.
你想多了
N0pe.
故事发生在牙买加的田野上...
The story begins on the fields of Jamaica Wherem
大卫又要演 “修水营” 这一套?
Davids is gonna do Ieaky pipes?
通常是很有效的
Usually Works, yeah.
你还是认为
You're still maintaining thatm
口香糖是给牛和低能儿吃的吗?
gum is for coWs and imbeciles?
对 而且这是事实
l do and it is.
滚开 我在睡觉
Go awaM Im s/eep/ng.
听得懂人话吗 我在睡觉
Come on, /7775/eep/ng.
抱歉打扰您了 瓦斯克兹先生
Sorry to bother you, Mr. VasqueZ,
但是您的公寓有地方在漏水
but there's a leak coming from your apartment
我需要迸来检查一下管道
l need to come in and check the pipes.
我没看见任何地方漏水了
/ don 't See any /ea/(5.
是房东雇我来的
The super hired me to check the pipes.
让我进去 我尽快修好的
Let me in and l'Il take care of it as quick as l can.
瓦斯克兹先生
Mr. VasqueZ?
先生
Sir.
请让我 进去检查一下管道
l need to get in there and check those pipes.
瓦斯克兹先生
Mr. VasqueZ.
我在穿衣服
/ m getting dressed
不许动 警察
Police. Don't move.
你的手不能再动了 明白?
Don't move your arm again, comprende?
知道了
AIl right. Yeah.
安东尼
Anthony.
你们搞什么
Bu‖shit, man. Shit.
屋里还有谁
Anybody else in there?
我女朋友
她在 卧室里 就只有她
She's in the bedroom, man. lt'sjust her.
那个被你抛弃的美女 她有武器吗?
She got a Weapon? This Wonderful Woman you're abandoning?
没有
No.
她叫什么
What's her name?
要是你还想的起来的话
If you happen to reca‖.
你们他妈难道想...
I\/lan, you Wanna get your fuckingm
操了
shitl
你靴子上有东西
There's something on your boot
我注意到了 她叫什么
Yeah, l noticed. What's her name?
- 罗斯琳达 - 这听起来像是两个名字
- Rosalinda. - That sounds like tWo names.
- 至少两个 - 只有一个人
- At Ieast. - Yeah. We‖, it'sjust one.
你确定里面只有一个女的
You're completely sure there's only one Woman in there?
就一个 只有她
Just one, man, it'sjust her.
罗斯琳达
Rosalinda.
我是博尔奥克警局的
This is the BulWark Police.
把门打开 举起双手 从房间走出来
l need you to open that door and come out With your hands up.
罗斯琳达 你在里面吗
Rosalinda, are you in there?
她会说英语吗
Rosalinda speaks English?
会 但她耳朵有点毛病
Yeah, yeah, but she got a problem With her ears, man.
- 她聋了吗 - 她平时戴助听器 警官
- ls she deaf? - She Wears something, man,
但是她睡觉时候不戴
to make her hear better but not When she goes to sleep though.
这个胖子看起来就是那种睡觉打呼噜的
He Iooks Iike a snorer.
那叫睡眠呼吸中止症
Yeah, it's ca‖ed sleep apnea, man.
她有枪吗
She got a firearm in there?
没有 但是她包里有防狼喷雾
No gun, man, but she got some pepper spray in her purse,
所以你懂的
so, you knowm
- 缚太紧 企缓之 - 缚虎焉能不紧
- Oh. Come on. Come on, man. - This Will be snug.
紧的我的血液都不流通 了
Shit, that's cutting off my circulation.
我们会在你腿变紫色之前回来
We'‖ be back before your foot turns blue.
别抱太大希望
Probably.
比我住的地方好多 了
A Iot nicer than my place.
味道都要好闻一些
Even the sme‖.
把大卫放进来吧
We'Ve met Davids.
- 警官? - 警探?
- Officer? - DeteCflVe?
演水管工人你实在是太入戏了
You dove deep on this plumber thing.
我有个表弟就是干这个的
l'Ve got a cousin Who plumbs.
把瓦斯克兹铐上了吗?
Vasquez a shackle?
铐在消防通道了
On the fire escape.
他的聋子女友还在里面
His deaf girlfriend's in here.
你们要枪击她吗?
You guys gonna shoot her?
- 她有枪吗 - 十有八九是有的
- She's got a gun. - 75-percent chance, yeah.
行吧 想让我帮你们干点几什么
All right. Where do you Want me?
守着窗户
WindoW.
他就应该让 "水管工” 进来的
Should've let the plumber ín.
我们是警察
Police. Okay?
能听懂吗
Comprende Si or no?
她的包有点儿沉
Her handbag seemed a little heavy.
拉美洲女人的化妆品都很多
You been taking into account the amount of make-up
- 你有考虑进去吗? - 就算有也不可能这么重
- Latinas carry? - Yeah, even sti‖.
包里有枪
She's got a gun.
宝贝 过来
Come on. Come on, honey.
在这儿别动
You stay there.
把门关上 风扇开到最大
Why don't you shut the doors and crank up the fans?
你男朋友昨晚交给你的绿色帆布袋
Where did your novío put that green duffel bag
放哪儿了?
you got Iast night?
能给我件衣服穿吗?
Can l haVe something to Wear?
我冷
l'm cold.
我没听懂他说的 你听懂了么
l didn't understand that, did you?
没有
No.
她好像在说 “海豚” 什么的
Sounded kind of like dolphin.
如果她能老实回答我们的问题
l eXpect she'‖ get more intelligible
或许她说的话会更好懂一些
When she ansWers 0ur questions.
- 绿的帆布袋在哪儿 - 我要见我的律师
- Where's the green duffel bag? - l'm gonna call a IaWyer.
我想
I Wannam
绿帆布袋在哪儿
Where's the green duffel bag?
我们亲眼看见瓦斯克兹 昨晚十一点把它带到这儿来了
We saW Vasquez bring it here Iast níght at 11:O0,
就是那个要抛弃你 自己逃跑的混蛋
that sWe‖ guy Who fled and Ieft you here With us.
选择灵魂伴侣
You see, a timem
还需谨慎
...to get a soulmate.
趁我和我搭档
Tell us Where it is
还能赶上波尔特家的早餐特供
and my partner and l Will be done in time
赶快把帆布袋的位置告诉我们
to get the breakfast special at Bert's.
也许我们能网开一面 不去追究你的责任
Maybe that's reason enough to forget a‖ about you
你包里的枪我们也权当没看见
and that gun of yours.
它在哪儿?
Where is it?
衣橱里
The closet.
那边
There.
在西装后面的墙里
ln the Wa‖ behind the suits.
我己经能闻到双面煎蛋的香昧了
l smell three eggs over easy.
还有土豆泥
Hash brownsm
还有全麦面包土司
and pumpernickel toast.
还有你欠我的那杯咖啡
Plus that coffee you oWe me.
- 警宫 - 警探?
- Officer. - DeteCflVe?
把瓦斯克兹押进来
Drag VasqueZ back inside.
我们要把赃款 毒品和这两个笨蛋
We got cash, narcotics, and tWo imbeciles
带回局里并且具结画押
to drive doWntoWn and paper.
你答应我的 如果我告诉你东西在哪儿就放了我的
You said íf l told you Where the bag Was you'‖ let me go.
- 你能听懂她说什么吗 - 不能
- Can you understand her? - No.
这歌是男的还是女的唱的
This a guy or a girl singing this song?
不好说
Can't te‖.
反正这年代是男是女已经不重要 了
Not that there's much of a difference these days.
我觉得底线已经没有 了
lthink that Iine Was obliterated.
自从男人开始说我们怀孕 了” 那天起 底线消失了
The day men started saying, "We're pregnant,"
但真正怀孕的是他们的老婆
When their Wives Were.
你们的早餐特供
Your breakfast specials.
谢谢
Thanks.
没想到警督对这些谣言这么感兴趣
Didn't knoW the Chief Lieutenant Was so fond of intrigue.
不好意思
Excuse me.
麻烦您帮我们打包一下 好吗?
Could you boX our food up in to-go containers?
我刚刚那么费劲地把餐盘给你们拿过来
You Want me to pack up everything
你们现在居然要我打包?
ljust carried from all the Way oVer there?
正确
Correct.
我去拿打包盒
l'Il get some take-out boXes.
你们俩是开车撞进早餐店了吗 身上一股食物的味道
You tW0 crashed into a truck filled With breakfast buffet?
我们俩刚才在波尔特家吃早餐特供
We Were getting the breakfast specials at Bert's
然后就收到了你的消息
When We got your message
我们就让服务员打包了 开车来的路上也反思了很久
and We boxed them up and rode in With the ruminations.
我很喜欢他家的面包土司
l Iike their pumpernickel toast.
他们是街对面的面包店
They get it fresh from 」eanette's,
珍妮特糕点买的
bakery across the Way.
你们俩今夭早的逮捕行动出问题了
There's an issue With the bust you tWo made this morning.
谁又投诉了
Who's complaining?
群众反映的 他们看见你们俩在消防通道上
Civílian, saW you out on the fire escape.
瓦斯克兹荷枪实弹是一个实实在在的威胁
Vasquez Was armed and a threat.
- 我们的做法没错 - 他拍了录像
- We did What Wasm - There's a Video.
你看过了吗
You've seen it?
看了 不算太糟
I have. lt's not terrible.
但也不算太妙
Certainly could be much, much better.
好在收音效果很烂
Sound is shit.
那个市民离现场很远 没录到什么关键信息
Civílian Was too far aWay to get anything inte‖igible.
- 这对我们来说是个好事儿 - 谁告的密
- That helps us. - Who tipped you off?
我在第七频道的联系人
My contact at Channel 7.
河边无青草 哪来的多嘴驴
Anchovies.
- 节目什么时候播出 - 六点
- When's it airing? - Six o'clock.
你们死不了
You'Il survive.
不过 我们之前谈的升职加薪的事情
Though, l think it'll end our current discussions
可能就得缓一缓了
about raises and promotions.
干他妈的多嘴驴
Anchovies.
我们没太为难瓦斯克兹
We didn't give Vasquez that much cast-iron.
- 主要是我 安东尼他...- 他也没少使坏
- lt Was mostly me, Anthonym - He gave him plenty.
卢拉赛提先生也在视频里
Mr. Lurasetti's in that video, too,
当你把脚踩在那位仁兄的脸上时
smiling Iíke a yearbook picture
他在旁边笑的跟花儿似的
When you put your foot on that hombrek cabeza
咱们的督察员
Our inspectorm
就是那位墨西哥裔的督察员 好像对此非常不满
our MeXican-American inspector, is unlikely to be Ienient.
虽然你们的办案效率非常值得褒奖 但这也只能让你们
Though your productivity is eXemplary and it'‖ keep you
免于丢掉工作
from Iosing your badges.
就像以前一样 还是政治问题
Politics like alWays.
就跟手机一样 处处扰人
Like cell phones andjust as annoying,
但却无处不在
politics are everyWhere.
被舆论定下种族歧视的罪名
Being branded a racist in today's public forum
就像在50年代被指控为共产主义分子一样要命
is Iike being accused of communism in the '50s
不论你只是在手机上发表了一条
Whether it's a possibly offensive remark
带有冒犯色彩的言论 还是你真的实施了类似
made in a private phone ca‖ 0r the indelicate treatment
卖毒品给小孩这样的龌龊行为
of a minority Who se‖s drugs to children.
像这种娱乐产业 特别是新闻
The entertainment industry, formerly knoWn as the neWs,
- 需要这样的恶人来当反面教材 - 这些媒体
- needs vi‖ains. - There's certainly nothing
就喜欢断章取义 妄下结论 随便给人贴标签
hypocritical about the media handling every perceived
这可真是一种伪善的做法啊
intolerance With complete and utter intolerance.
简直就是胡来
lt's bu‖shit.
可这就是现实
But it's reality.
但我不是种族主义者
But l'm not racist.
就连每个马丁路德金日我都会点一杯焦糖咖啡呢
Every Martin Luther King Day l order a cup of dark roast.
这次停职多久
HoW long is this suspension gonna be?
6个星期
Six Weeks.
不带薪
No pay.
工作时长得给我们算上
We need the hours.
这个不用你教 我懂
l knoW What detectives make and more.
去吃点面包吧
Go have some pumpernickeL
瑞支曼
Ridgeman.
以后你得注意一点了
Gotta be aWare of this stuff.
现在到处都是摄像头
Digital eyes are everyWhere.
我出去执行任务的时候的所作所为都是我认为最合适的
ldo What l think best When l'm out there.
我们之前搭档 的时候 我就这样
l Was that Way When We Were partners
现在我也没变
and l'm still that Way noW.
这就是为什么我坐在这个桌子里面当领导
There's a reason I'm sitting behind this desk running things
而你只能跟一个比你小四岁的搭档在这么冷的天
and you're out there crouching on fire escapes
爬上消防道执行任务
in the cold for hours
这都是有原因的
With a partner that's 20 years younger than you.
嘿 安东尼虽然满嘴跑火车 但他是个老实人
Hey, Anthony's got a mouth With its oWn engine but he's solid.
这不是我想说的重点
That Wasn't my point.
感谢你把这个情况提前告知我们
Thanks for Ietting us knoW about this situation
如果你能在督察员那里 帮我们说说好话的话
and any Word you can have With the inspector on our behalf
那就真是感激不尽
Would be greatly appreciated.
在你走之前 还有一个事儿
One thing before you go.
我看了那个视频很多遍
l Watched that Video a couple times.
你有好几次都采取了没有必要的镇压措施
You threW a Iot more cast-iron than you needed to.
我们之前搭档的时候
And When We Worked togetherm
你也没有这么强硬啊
you Weren't that rough.
所以呢
And?
一直负重前行
lt's not healthy for you
对你来说不健康
to scuff concrete as Iong as you have.
虽然这么做得到了你想要的结果
You get results,
但同 时你会失去明察事理的能力和怜悯心
but you're losing perspective and compassion.
再过几年 你就会变成一个满身是刺
Couple more years out there and you're gonna be
以愤怒为燃料 只会以强硬措施打压他人的
a human steamroller covered Wíth spikesm
破案机器
and fueled by bile.
外面要抓的坏蛋可多了去了
There's a Iot of imbeciles out there.
好吧
Yeah.
好好利用这段时间 想想我说的这些话
Use your time off to think about things.
跟梅拉妮聊聊这事儿
Talk it over With l\/lelanie.
多陪陪她和萨拉
Spend some time With her and Sara.
我会的
Yeah, l Wi‖.
不要生气
lWon't.
平常心
l Won't.
萨拉
Sara?
妈妈 是我
Yeah, Mom, it's me.
宝贝
SWeetie?
怎么了
What's Wrong?
宝贝
SWeetie?
过来
Come here.
晚上好 欢迎回来 卢拉赛提先生
Good evening. And Welcome back, I\/lr. Lurasetti.
所有在纽约出生的人
Anybody bom in NeW York
- 都叫我托尼 - 好 那就叫你托尼
- ca‖s me Tony. - Tony it is.
请您稍等
One moment, please.
戒指有问题吗 托尼
ls something Wrong With it, Tony?
没有 戒指很美 跟你之前承诺的一样
No, no, it's beautifuL Exactly Iike you promised.
如果我在单膝下跪 向丹尼斯求婚的时候
It's... lf Denise has any doubts about saying yes
她有半分的迟疑
When l'm on my knee, this Will
这枚戒指一定能帮忙坚定她的决心
nudge her in the ríght direction.
我工作上出了点问题
l got an issue at Work.
您需要分期付款吗
Do you need a payment plan?
- 我很乐意为您... - 不了谢谢
- l'd be more than happy to... - Thanks.
钱我存够了 不是钱的问题 是别的问题
I saved enough for this. lt's a different kind of problem.
我老婆有两个当大夫的兄弟
My Wífe has tW0 brothers Who are therapists
三个当律师的姐妹
and three sisters Who Were IaWyers.
呃 我的问题他们解决不了
We‖, my problems don't require those kinds of professionals.
我只是想到我能为我女朋友
ljustm I'm thinking about the kínd of future
提供的物质生活 肯定是负担不起
l can offer my girlfriend and, you knoW,
太多珠宝 所以我很担心
that Iife Won't have a Iot of diamonds.
2B保险箱储物状况: 己确认 储存时间: 未知
你明天晚上之前-定要准备就绪
You must be ready by tomorroW night
好的 这里你一定要小心
Okay. You gotta be careful around these parts.
有狮子
lt's got Iions.
能杀它们吗
Can We shoot them?
能 但除非你有猎枪
Well, yeah. But it's gonna be pretty hard
不然是很难杀的
unless you have a pump-action shotgun.
那我们去弄一把...见鬼
Not if We get onem Oh, shit.
看好了 躲我身后来
Okay, Iook. Get behind me.
呆在那儿
Okay, stay there.
小家伙可以嘛
Nigga iced that feline.
咱们得走了 会来更多狮子的
Okay, lo0k, We gotta go. There's more coming.
等我们过了河之后
Okay, 0nce you get across this stream,
就得去找蟒蛇 了
We gotta look out for boa constrictors.
你简直都可以直接去野外狩猎了
This nigga's ready for a real safari.
就算我的腿没事儿
Even if my Iegs Worked right
我也不想真的去打猎
lWouldn't Wanna be hunting animals for real.
这是那些富豪白人的消遣活动
It's Iike some rich White people shit.
不过 这游戏你玩的还是很6的
Still, you're real good at this game.
我们玩的其他几款游戏 你也很厉害
And the other ones We played, too.
那当然 我长大之后就想干这个
Well, yeah, this is What I Wanna d0 When l groW up.
- 玩游戏吗? - 不 当一个游戏设计师
- Play games? - N0. No, be a game designer.
去创造与现实世界
To create Worlds that are,
不一样的世界
you knoW, different from the outside.
有学校是专门教这个的 对吧
There's schools that teach you hoW to do that?
- 大学还是什么? - 嗯 是有专门的培训学校
- Co‖ege or something? - Yeah. They got schools.
等你高中毕业 我就...
Maybe once you finish high school, you canm
我得走了
l gotta g0_
能保存么
Can you save this adventure?
能存
Yeah. l can save it.
好
AIl right.
他表弟这一次也要去
His cousins are gonna be there this time.
我知道
Yeah, they are.
我不喜欢做
ldon't Iike doing things
这种充满未知的事情
With so many question marks eVeryWhere.
我也不喜欢
Yeah. Me neither.
但他们己经开始行动了
But they Was moved up.
预付款你也拿到 了
You already got our advances.
还有 安德雷帮这几个人做了担保
Plus, Andrei already vouched for 'em.
安德雷这个人本身就挺不可信的
Andrei himself is questionable.
你带 "安保工具”了吗
You got our insurance?
在贮物箱里
ln the glove compartment
为什么要用玻璃纸包着枪
Why'd you Want them Wrapped in ce‖ophane?
为了防止没时间戴手套 或者擦除指纹的
There's some times a nigga ain't got time for glovesm
情况发生
or to Wipe things doWn.
没错 省去不少麻烦
Yeah. We don't need to use those.
一有机会 就把这几把枪藏到他们车上
We'II stash them in the vehicles When We get the chance.
包括逃跑要用的那辆车
The van and the get-aWay.
小菜一碟
lt's a‖ cotton candy.
今早一位博尔沃克的市民拍下了
The two detect/'l/e5 Were filmed by a concerned
两名警宫执法的过程
Bulwark cítlken this m0rning.
这两名警官目前已被停职
Both partners ha Ve been Suspended
布雷特 瑞支曼分别在1998年和2004年
Brett R/dgeman Was charged With excessive force
被指控暴力执法
m 7998 and 2004..
而安东尼 卢拉赛提去年也因 为违反行为准则
And Anthony Lurasetfl Was suspended for l//0/at/hg
而被停职接受调查
the code of conduct lastyean
警察局局长拒绝就此事发表评论...
The police c0mm/3S/0ner has declined to commentu
给你5秒钟 把收银柜里的钱交给我
You've got five seconds to hand me your draWer.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
Onem
TWOW
Threem
Fourm
-5-都是你的了
- FiVe. - Yours.
我想要一包
Oh, I rea‖y need a pack ofm
求求你
Please.
别杀我
脱鞋
Shoesl
我忘了
l forgot.
_嘿-嘿
_ Hey, - Hey.
- 喝啤酒吗 - 不了 谢谢
- Want a beer? - No, thanks.
我今天多吃了几颗药
l haVe to take some extra meds today.
怎么回事
l'm sorry to hear that.
你还好吗
Y0u Okay?
还好
Fair.
这些衣服是怎么回辜几
What's that about?
萨拉下了校车 在回家的路上受到几个小孩的威胁
Some kids Were menacing Sara on her Way back from the bus
其中一个向她脸上泼了一杯汽水
and one of them threW a cup of orange soda all over her.
- 什么孩子 - 她不认识
- What kids? - The one she didn't recognize.
四个黑人 其中一个骑着自行车
Four blacks, one on a bike.
而且现在弄清楚是谁真的重要吗 这都第五次 了
But does it actually matter Who? That's the fifth time.
操蛋的社区
This fucking neighborhood,
情况真是越来越糟 了
itjust keeps getting Worse and Worse.
- 她没事儿吧 - 没什么大事儿 不过
- Is she okay? - We‖, yeah. But,
让她放学后走4个街区的路回家 已经很辛苦了
coming home from school and Walking four blocks
- 现在还碰上这种事 - 我知道
- shouldn't be an ordeal. - No. It shouldn't.
你提议过她去车站接她 送她回家吗
Did you offer to pick her up at the bus, escort her back?
当然
Of course l did.
她知道要我走这么远的路很不方便
She knoWs it isn't easy for me to get around a lot
而且我去了 她也会尴尬
and she'd be too embarrassed anyWays.
老爸老妈都是警察 她这么要强不是没有道理
We‖, she's got tWo sets of cop DNA, so of course she's tough.
是啊 特别是考虑到她的性别和现在的年纪
Yeah, especially for her age and gender.
她再长大一点 会变得更有女人味
But she's getting older, more Womanly.
到时候那些男生 可能就会动其他的歪脑筋
And these boys are gonna start haVing different kinds of ideas
不仅仅是泼杯汽水这么简单了
about her pretty soon, if they don't already.
你知道么 在住进这里之前
You knoW, I never thought l Was a racist
我一直以为自己不是一个种族岐视者
before liVing in this area.
我跟其他退役警察不同 我的思想非常开朗 可现在...
l'm about as Iiberal as any eX-cop could ever be. But nowm
- 咱们真的得搬家了 - 我知道
- We really need to move. - l knoW.
我的意思是 马上搬
No. Yesterday or the day before.
我知道
l knoW.
但现如今你跟安东尼又闯了祸
Well, this thing that's going on With you and Anthony right noW,
- 这可真是雪上加霜 - 你看了那段录像了?
- it's not gonna help. - You saW the Vasquez footage?
- 看了 - 然后呢
-ldid.-And?
你真的该换件风衣 了
lt's rea‖y time you got a neW Windbreaker.
好吧
Yeah.
是有不少人这么说
A couple people made comments.
我之前绐博尔沃克安保公司的人
Well, l Was starting to say before
打了电话问他们
that l ca‖ed up Bulwark Security Provider
- 能不能... - 你不能去当保安
- and I asked themm - You're not doing security Work.
我们搬家 需要钱
We need m0ney to move.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
- 我可以吃止疼药 - 不行 你吃止疼药
- I can take painkillers if... - No. You're taking painkillers
去削个土豆什么的 我还同意 其他的免谈
to peel potatoes as it is. lt's not Worth debating.
可我真的很想做点什么
But l Wanna do something.
作为一个母亲 一个退役警察
l need to do something
我必须帮这个家 做点什么
as a mother, as a former cop.
否则总有一天 你我会跑到医院陪着女儿
Or someday, someday you and me We are in a hospital room
看着她接受强奸顾 问 的心理治疗
With our daughter talking to a rape counselor.
好吧
Yeah.
这事交给我吧
l'll handle this.
你要怎么处理
How?
我有办法
There's a Way.
不过这个办法 我不能跟你说
But it's not something that We're gonna talk aboutm
永远都不能说
eVe「.
好吧
Okay.
萨拉
Sara.
干嘛
)/ea/7?
那个演小狮子的节目开始了
That shoW about the lion cubs is on
你想不想和我一起看
if you Wanna Watch it With me.
如果你想看书的话那就算了
If you'd rather read that's, you knowm
没关系
No, it's fine.
反正这一页我己经盯了四分钟了
Been staring at the same page for the past 20 minutes anyWay.
想不想来点儿零食
Hey, you Want something to nibble?
好
Sure.
今天发生的事 你没关系吧
Are you okay With What happened?
我没事
Yeah, l'm fine.
嘿
Hey
- 来块饼干 - 不了 谢谢
- Do you Want a cookie? - No, thank you.
他们长大前 真是太可爱了
They're so cute before they get big.
我有差事得忙几个小时后就回来
l got an errand to run. Be back in a couple hours.
我是来找弗雷德里希的 或者他更喜欢别人叫他弗莱迪
l'm here to talk With Friedrich or Freddie if he prefers.
- 您怎么称呼 -告诉他瑞支曼来了
- And Who can l say is... - Tell him Ridgeman is here.
- 我看看他是否有空 - 他肯定有
- l'll go see if he's available. - He is.
这些衣服多少钱 我都没看到有价签
HoW much are these? l don't see a tag.
FiVe thousand do‖ars.
它们是防弹的吗
So they're bu‖etproof?
要喝一杯吗
You care for a drink?
我不是来喝酒的
l'm not here for a beverage.
请坐
Yes.
你是来买新西装的么
You're Iooking for a neW suit?
考虑到你通过暴力的方式赢得了一些休闲时间
NoW that you haVe violently earned some leísure time.
- 我没有 - 那你今晚为什么
- l'm not. - Why then have you decided
突然光临我的店
to inhabit my shop this evening?
你儿子还好吗
HoW's your son doing?
非常好
Well, Very We‖.
我和她妈妈
His mother and l
下个月要带他去看几所大学
are taking him to visit some campuses neXt month.
他考试考得很好
He scored very high on his tests.
我一直觉得他很有潜力
lthought he had potential.
谢谢
Thank you.
你不可能平白无故来找我说吧 什么事
l knoW that you're not ínclined toWards eXceptions.
他小时候犯了事 被抓进监狱里
Well, he Was a kíd, the ringleaders are in jail
我当 时放了他一马 因为我知道这么做能在未来的某个时候
and l kneW I could get something more valuable from you someday
从你这里得到更珍贵的东西
ifl Iet him slip through a crack.
- 有什么需要我帮助的? -我要-条线索
- HoW can l be of aid? - l need a Iead.
你想找什么?
And What are you hoping to find?
一个毒贩或者买家
A dealer, or a buyer.
最好不是本地人
Preferably one from out of toWn.
我不像以前那样消息灵通了
l am not as we‖-informed as l once Was.
那就打电话给知道的人
Ca‖ someone that is.
我试试吧
l sha‖.
就现在
NoW.
安东尼 是我
Anthony. Yeah.
4点半来我家门口接我
Be outside my place at 4:30.
对 早上
Yup1a'm'
把假牌照换上
Put on your fake Iicense plate.
装备带齐 穿着低调
Bring a‖ your hardWare and dress nonchalant
你是新闻上播的那个明星警察吗？
Are you the famous police officer l saW in the neWs?
你突然叫我出来 是有事吗?
Any reason you're back there?
对
There is.
你和悔拉妮没事吧
Things okay With you and Melanie?
没事
They're fine.
那你这次叫我出来到底是干什么?
Are you gonna tell me the nature of this endeavor?
我先睡会
l'm gonna sleep.
你到底要干...
你开去1 9大道布朗特街
You're gonna drive to 19th and Brant.
跑这么远干嘛?
Why are We going a‖ the Way up there?
我只要回答你一个问题
Every ansWer I giVe you
你就会冒出来更多的问题
is gonna engender three times as many questions.
我想趁现在补会觉
Let me sleep While l can and
到了目的地后 你的所有问题就会迎刃而解
once We're there, you'll get your ansWers
到时候你想补个觉也行
and a nap if you need one.
听起来像一个监视任务
Sounds Iike a stake out.
快去柏大道布朗特街
19th and Brant.
我们被停职了 你不会忘了吧
You realize We're suspended
到十八大道的时候 叫醒我
Wake me at 18th.
到十八大道了
We're at 18th.
前面右拐
Corner right.
先擦擦手
Before you touch anything.
垃圾桶
Ash tray.
我公寓附近也开了一家这种橘色商店
One of these big orange things opened up by my apartment
"每日鲜"
Ripe and Fresh.
- 很差劲吗 - 我没去逛过
- Shit? - l haVen't been in it.
德尼斯不是要做饭吗
lthought Denise cooked.
只在她家做
Only at her place.
她买食材只去那种有机商店
She only shops at organic stores
能够稍微减轻一些摄取热量的负罪感
that specialize in assuaging guilt.
停在这个垃圾桶的对面
Let's pull over the other side of this dumpster.
- 可以吗 - 完美
- ls this good? - It's perfect
吃两粒吧
Take tW0.
那栋灰色建筑里的633号房有蹊跷
Something's going on in Room 633 of that tan stucco.
什么蹊跷
What?
难说
Hard to te‖.
主要是因为那栋楼里根本就没有633号房
Especially because Apartment 633 doesn't even eXist.
此话怎讲
H0W do you mean?
那栋楼里没有633这个门牌
Well, there's no door marked 633.
没有窗户也没有 门铃
There's no WindoWs or a buzzen
甚至没有邮件曾邮寄过这个地方
No mail gets delivered there either.
但那个房间却存在
But it's there.
这听起来有点玄乎啊
This ís sounding metaphysicaL
你有线索吗
You got a tip on this?
有
Yeah.
我的线人告诉我 一个叫洛伦兹 沃格曼的人
My contact te‖s me that one Lorentz Vogelmann
正在找一处隐形住宅
is looking for an invisible residence.
这栋楼里的633号房就是他的根据地
And 633 in this tan stucco is Where he Ianded.
沃格曼 没听说过这个名字
Vogelmann, l don't knoW that name.
他不是本地人
Well, he's not local.
他干什么的
What Iine of Work is he in?
毒贩
Distribution.
主要分销海洛因
Heroin mostly.
数额巨大
Large bundles.
咱们来这儿干什么
What are We doing here?
你是以平民的身份问我这个问题吗
You asking me this question as a civilian?
因为这就是现实 我们就是平民
Because that's What We are right noW, civilians.
跟那些幼儿园老师 或者在我家门口
N0 different than kindergarten teachers or the bum
捡易拉罐的流浪汉亳无差别
that collects aluminum cans outside my buílding.
咋天我把警徽给上交了我又不是忘了
l knoW Where l flung my badge yesterday.
到底咱们来这干什么
What are We doing here?
我们正在监视一个嫌疑人
We're monitoring a suspicious individual
看他是否拥有一笔目前还用不上的资金
to try and figure out if he's got any money he doesn't need.
简直吃饱了撑的
Anchovies.
- 你要是不想干 - 天哪
- If you don't Wanna be part of... - Christ.
你疯了吗
Are you ínsane?
你被停职了 而且这己经不是你职业生涯中
You get suspended, not for the first time
第一次被停职了
in your career either.
现在你居然还想变成一个罪犯?
NoW you decide to become a criminal?
你到底在打什么主意?
And What the hell are you even thinking With this?
嗯
We‖...
解释一下
Say something.
说话
Talkl
我还有一个月就60岁了
l'm a month aWay from my 60th...
我的官衔却停留在了我27岁那年
l'm still the same rank l Was at 27.
多年来 我一直相信只要保证工作质量
For a Iot of years, l believed that the quality of my Work,
好好跟你合作 跟我之前的搭档合作
What We do togethen What l did With my previous partnersm
能够让我获得我应得的回报
Would get me What I deserved.
但是我不会说场面话 也不懂得与时俱进
But I don't politic and l don't change With the times.
结果发现 原来这些虚的比诚恳的工作
And it turns out that that shit's more important
更重要
than good honest Work.
所以昨天我们虽然阻止了一场
So yesterday, after We stop a massive amount of drugs
大量毒品流入学校的犯罪事件
from getting into the school system,
我们还是被停职了 就因为我们的做法"不礼貌”
We get suspended because it Wasn't done politely.
我回家后 发现我女儿经历了这两年来的
When l go home and l find my daughter has been assaulted
第五次被骚扰
for the fifth time in tWo years
全都是因为我这少得可怜的工资
Because of the shit neighborhood
被追让她生活在那个糟糕的社区
my shit Wage has forced me to Iive in.
而我的妻子根本帮不上忙
And my Wife can't help.
她现在只能勉强依靠药物维持生活
She's barely getting through the day on her meds as it is.
她们没事吧
They okay?
梅拉妮还应付得了 萨拉心态也很好
Yeah. Melanie's coping. Sara's doing okay.
好在她比同龄人要成熟很多
She's dealing With it better than most kids her age Would.
不过这样长期下去 谁知道会对她的
But Who knoWs What kind of long-term damage
身心造成多大的伤 害
is going on With her.
以前类似的机会有很多 还不是一次两次
There has been opportunities before, more than a feW.
受贿 贪污 顺手牵羊
Take a bribe, pocket a bundle, pilfer cash.
我以前是一个出外勤警察 现如今我只是一个年近60的
lWas a cop on actiVe duty. Today, l'm a poor civilian
可怜平民
Who's nearly 60.
我能接受贫穷
l can accept that,
但是我不能让我的妻子女儿和我一起承受
but l'm not gonna ask my Wife and daughter to.
要是把我们俩一起破过的案子
lf We put a‖ our collars togethen
一起抓到的罪犯加在一起
every imbecile We ever nabbed,
差不多都够关满州监狱的两间大牢房了
it'd probably fill tWo entire Wings
甚至是3间
of the state prison. Maybe three.
我们有实力 也有权利 要求适当的补偿
We have the skills and the right to acquire proper compensation.
- 天哪 - 结婚可不便宜
- Christ. - Weddings aren't cheap.
少犯浑了 我想的不是这个问题
Don't be an asshole. That's not What l'm thinking about
你觉得 我们现在的工资和我们的付出成正比吗
Do you think our Wages accurately reflect What We did?
别跟我说这些
Enough With thejustifications.
我比你聪明多了
I'm smarter than you by a yard stick,
休想给我洗脑
you're not gonna manipulate me.
我看到了你昨天看那个帆布袋的眼神
l saW hoW you looked at that duffel bag yesterday.
闭嘴
Quiet.
让我想想
Let me think.
巧舌如簧
Anchovies.
如果你不想再听到我说这些
Look, if you don't Wanna hear any more about this,
你可以马上开车 把我扔在这里
fling the gear and drop me off.
- 我不想让你受伤 - 我不需要保镖
- l don't Want you to get hurt. - l don't need a guardian.
如果可以的话 我一个人也能干
l can do this myself ifl have to.
那可不一定
You don't knoW that.
没错 是不一定会成功 但如果情况有变
Not for sure, no. But if things get tricky,
我能立马抽身 再想其他办法
I'll disengage and find something else.
这不是个好主意
This is a bad idea.
对你 对我都不好
lt's bad for you, and it's bad for me.
这个主意简直是烂到无以复加
lt's bad Iíke lasagna in a can.
那就开车吧 把我一个人扔在这里就行
Well, then, fling the gear and drop me off.
如果你要干 你一定要为自己而干
Lo0k, if you do this, you do ít for yourself.
不用同情我的处境 然后选择加入
You don't do it because you pity my situation.
也不能因为我们是搭档 或者我们是一起在周日
Or because We're partners or because We're friends
烤汉堡 一起练拳击的朋友才选择加入
that grill burgers on Sundays, or go t0 the fights.
你必须是因为你自己也想赚钱才选择加入的
You do it solely because you Wanna earn. And that's it.
我们在行动的时候必须乔装改扮
We disguise ourselves at the point of contact
我在垃圾袋里 防弹面具与防弹背心
Yeah, I got ballistic masks and vests in the garbage bags,
还有几颗催泪弹
some teargas bombs as We‖.
那我暂时加入吧
l'm in until l'm not.
- 洛伦兹 沃格曼 - 对
- Lorentz Vogelmann? - Yeah.
他看起来是个强硬派
He looks cast iron.
对
He is.
你确定他的货都藏在633号房吲
Any idea if his merchandise is in 633?
不确定 但一旦我们确认他就住在这里
No idea, but after We confirm that he's there,
我们就可以尾随他 进而掌握他的行程轨迹
We'Il tail him and We'll Iearn his itinerary.
你有时间表吗
You got a timeframe?
我的线人说他交了两个星期的租金
I\/ly contact said he's rendered 633 for tWo Weeks.
今天是第二天
We're at day tWo of that period.
你还知道他的别的信息吗 比如开什么车 社会关系什么的?
You knoW anything else about him, vehicles, associates?
这就是我们现在要掌握的信息
That's What We're Iearning n0W.
摄像机昵
Camera?
谢谢
Thanks.
你快睡一会吧
Why don't you take a nap?
求之不得
Gladly_
醒了记得问问我还要不要和你一起干
Make sure to ask me if l'm still in When l Wake up.
我都快睡了五个小时了
l'Ve been processing here for five hours.
你应该叫 醒我的
You should have given me a nudge.
没这个必要
There Wasn't a reason to.
你还加入吗
Are you still in?
暂时加入
Iam until l'm not.
- 看见沃格曼了吗 - 还没有
- You see Vogelmann yet? - Nope.
我要去那个橘色便利店买点东西
l'm gonna get something from this big orange thing.
你要加了蛋黄酱的黑麦吐司 吗
You Want egg salad on rye toast?
帮我买两片外加一瓶沙士
TWo of them, and root beer.
阿门
Amen.
过去98分钟里 我一直在听你吧唧嘴的声音
l'Ve been Iistening to and sme‖ing that
还一直闻 到食物的昧道
for the last 98 minutes.
监视最爽的地方就是
Best part of a stake out,
除了最后任务结束的时候
other than When it endsm
就是吃东西的 时候了
is When you're eating.
一只蚂蚁都比你吃的快一些
A single red ant could've eaten it faster.
不是他
Nope.
吃两粒吧
Take tW0.
我还在享受口中的余味
I'm still enjoying the aftertaste.
我一点都不享受
Not all of us are.
你把车停哪儿了
Where did you park?
我就说吧 你越来越健忘了
I've been telling you, you're getting senile.
你没锁吗
You didn't Iock it?
我忘
I form
我之前在想其他的事 抱歉
IWas thínking about something else at the time. Sorry.
这是你的包?
This your duffel?
不是
Idon't think so.
面向挡风玻璃
Face the Wíndshield.
系上安全带 锁好车门
Put on your seat belts and lock the doors.
帕科
Pacom
麻烦你把遮阳布拉上
put up that sunshade, por favon
很好 现在把口袋里的钱都拿出来
Good. NoW empty your pockets.
把所有东西都放到包里
Put everything in that duffel bag,
不然我就送你去见上帝
or you'll be painting houses in heaven.
求你不要杀我
No, please.
给你们5秒
You have five seconds.
Fourm
- 3 - 这是我全部家当了
- Threem - That's a‖ l got.
我也是 我发誓
l\/le to0, I sWear to God.
把口袋翻出来看看
Show me your pocket Whites.
看见了吗
See?
把手机关了
Shut off that phone.
再见
Bye.
我还以为你
I expected youm
你要
You'Il f...
彻底没气了
Airless.
请允许我为你展示一下车的内部状况
Please, a‖oW me to shoW you the ínterior.
如果里面有活物
If anything moves in there,
老鼠
a 「at, a mOUSe,
或者蚊子
a baby mosquito,
我就送你去见阿拉
you'll get to ring A‖ah's doorbe‖.
把引擎盖打开
P0p the hood.
还满意吗?
All is as expected?
这血是附送的吗
The blood is gratis.
钥匙
Keys.
布雷特 是你吗
Brett, that you?
是的
Confirmed.
看看衣柜里 我给你准备了一个惊喜
Look in the closet, I got you something.
试试看
Try it on.
你买的都很合身
Everything you get me fits perfect
谢谢你帮我买衣服
Thanks for getting it.
在床上谢我吧
Thank me in bed.
你们今天有去欺负那些有色族裔的人吗?
S0, did you guys beat up any minorities today?
我们只有在执行任务的的时候才这么干
That's only When We're on the clock.
- 这个太好吃了 - 你喜欢就好
- This Was really delicious. - Glad you Iiked it.
考虑到你现在这种沉默寡言的状态
And should l infer from your reticence
我推测这一次你又不方便谈论你的工作吧?
this is one of those times you can't talk about your Work?
得了吧 我哪有沉默寡言
Please, infer about my reticence.
虽然你被停职了
Even though you've been suspended
但严格来讲 你普通人的身份没被剥夺吧?
and you're technically a civilian?
罪犯不会因为两个誓察被停职
Criminals don't stop doing What they do
就不再犯罪了
just 'cause tWo cops get benched.
而且我们警察也不是为了拿工资才接受这份工作的
And We don't do What We dojust for the paycheck.
怎么了
What?
别拿这种哄小孩的话来搪塞比你聪明的人
Don't try and bluff somebody Who's smarter than you are.
我可比你聪明多了
Smarter by a yardstick.
你有没有看到我从西奥伦佐家买了奶油煎饼卷?
Did you see l brought cannolis from Theo Renzo's?
别做自毁前途的事就好
Just don't do anything tojeopardize your career, please.
我不会的
lWon't.
还有7个车位没人用
Seven unaccounted for.
如果沃格曼真的住在那个楼里
lf Vogelmann's in that tan stucco
他有车的话 其中一个车位一定是他的
and oWns a vehicle, one of them is his.
你没打退堂鼓吧
Are you still in?
己经在要退不退的边缘了
At the outermost edge.
因为德尼斯
Denise?
她好像猜到了我有什么事瞒着她
She guessed that something Wasn't right.
我只字未提
Ididn't say anything.
所以昵
So?
我己经把订婚戒指了取回来了
Picked up the engagement ríng.
- 从费因鲍姆珠宝店? - 对
- From Feinbaum? - Yeah.
行吧
我们被停职那天去取的
Got it the day We busted, uh, Vasquez andm
时机不算太好但是...
We‖, the timing Wasn't great, butm
我想着这个婚早晚都要求 我不想因为工作上的不顺
IWas gonna propose anyWay, I Wasn't gonna let some
来影响我的个人生活 结果...
Work bullshit interfere With my private Iife, but turned outm
那晚她碰巧因为工作上的一些纠纷
she Was in a bad mood that night
心情非常的不好 所以我没有求
because of some drama at herjob, and l didn't do it.
然后昨天你又把我带到这几来 提议干这个事儿
And then yesterday you bring me here, suggest this thing,
虽然我并不抗拒 我感觉从那些
and l'm sort of okay With the idea,
人渣毒贩手里抢些钱 也算不上伤天害理的事
us taking money off some fuckhead dealer.
如果风险不是很大的话
lf the risk isn't too great.
但昨天晚上
But, you knoW, that night,
当我看见德尼斯 在她起疑心之前
When I see Denise, even before she suspected anythingm
我就意识到必须等到这一切结束 我才能向她求婚
l knoW that I can't propose to her until this thing is done.
我当时回避了她的问题 自我从珠宝店回来之后
I evade her questions at dinner and for the first time
只有在那一刻
since I Went to the jewelerm
我才突然动摇了 怀疑她是否会答应我的求婚
I'm n0t certain she'd say yes ifl proposed.
好了 我送你回家
Yeah. I'm driving you home.
我还没做好决定昵 我只是在犹豫...
l haven't made a decision yet. l'mjust ponderingm
放屁 你早就心里做好决定了
Bu‖shit. You're decíded, even if you think you aren't.
你比我年轻 你有更多的选择
You're younger than me, you've got more options.
等我们复职之后 你就申请换一个新搭档
Request a neW partner When We're back on duty,
说不定你以后还能混个巡官当当
they'll probably make you a sergeant one day.
我不想换搭档
l don't Want a neW partner.
我也跟你说过 我要跟你一起完成这项任务
And l told you that l'd finish out the shift
我很感激 但是你没有义务和责任非要这么做
Yeah, l appreciate it. But look, you're not obligated.
- 我别无选择 - 我的口头承诺就是一种责任
- I haVe done it Withm - My Word is an obligation.
谢谢
Thanks.
两片蛋黄酱面包
TWo egg salads,
如果你不买生香肠 你的那份我就请了
and I'II pay for yours, too, if it's not Sobrasada.
来车了
Here's one.
他在停车
This guy's parking.
这两个人看起来很可疑
These brothers have seen some stuff.
嗯 他们有问题
Yeah, they're taínted.
你觉得他们是沃格曼的人吗
Think they're With Vogelmann?
还是他的买家
His buyers?
有20%的可能性 但也有可能是中间人
TWenty-percent. Go-betWeens or Iocal muscles
或者打手
probably more like it.
再买两杯沙士
And tWo root beers.
没有退路了
No choice.
瑞支曼
Ridgeman?
- 是沃格曼吗 - 对
- Vogelmann? - Yeah.
还有之前的那两个黑人
The black dudes We saW before.
他们往西走了
They're going West.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
这辆破车需要上点润滑油 了
The grey lady needs a decongestant
开慢点 不要打草惊蛇
Don't giVe 'em a Wedgie.
现在减速的话反倒会引起他们的怀疑
Driving any sloWer than this Will get us noticed.
这片儿我不熟 西面到底有什么
l don't knoW this area real We‖. What's West?
再往前面开一截
Well, more of this.
就有一条高速公路之后是学区
Then the turnpike and then the school district.
希望他们不是大费周章去学校偷蜡笔
Probably not doing all this to steal crayons.
我们要不要先约法三章
You feel like some construction Work?
你觉得有必要吗
ls that necessary right noW?
没什么必要
FiVe percent
难道不需要为之后可能遇到的情况制定一个行为标准
That's for shooting out tires, sending a Warning,
比如交火 发出警告什么的?
things like that, right?
我们不会做出任何出格行为的
We're not going after any precedence.
我需要一个更肯定的答案
I need a better ansWer than that.
现在我们正驶向一片未知区域
Ríght noW, We're heading into neW territory.
期间我们可能会碰上任何情况我很清楚自己的底线
Foggy gray Iandscape, but l knoW all of my limits,
但是我不知道你的
but maybe not yours.
所以在我像参军的时候那样
So before l build a killing instrument
启动杀人模式之前
that l Iast used in the army,
我必须要你亲口保证在你实施抢劫的过程中
lwanna hear that you don't plan on executing a human being
你没有计划杀死任何一个人
to facilitate a robbery.
我们绝不杀人
We're not executing anybody.
好 这条准则必须用钢筋混凝土加固
That boundary is reinforced in steel concrete.
同意加固
Agreed. NoW, build.
他们在拼车车道那辆黑色SUV的旁边
The carpool Iane. Right by the black SUV.
把枪收起来 别走火了
Don't Iet that catch you cold.
你觉得他们今天是来交易的吗?
You think the transactions happened today?
看起来挺像
Oh, this is business.
两个行为可疑的黑人和另一个外地罪犯
TWo tainted black dudes and an out-of-toWn convict
在天亮前驱车外出
going for a drive before daWn.
虽然很有可能只是初步行动
Although it's probablyjust a preliminary.
沃格曼上车前 手里拿着两个黑色的公文包
Vogelmann Was carrying tWo black briefcases When he got in.
你还有什么事情是忘了告诉我的
ls there anything else you forgot to te‖ me?
- 没了 - 你确定
- No. - No. Are you sure?
比如说一些细节 比如那两个黑人中有人
Something subtle, Iike maybe one of the black dudes
- 带着火箭筒 -嘿
- had a bazooka? - Hey.
我盯了好几个小时的哨 而且你一直在打呼 我突然忘了嘛
IWas up for hours listening t0 you process air. lt escaped me.
行吧
Fine.
我想你应该全程都不叫醒我
And l suppose you could haVe Iet me sleep through all of this,
自己一个人把事情搞定
and been done With the Whole thíng.
我确实应该不叫醒你
l definitely should have.
考虑到公文包的出现
Considering the bríefcasesm
有百分之七十的概率他们今天要进行交易
seventy percent this is the transaction.
剩下的百分之三十昵
What's the other 30?
那个公文包里装的可能是现金 也可能是毒品
Vogelmann maybe shoWing somebody some cash, or some merchandise,
所以沃格曼要么是去卖毒品 要么就是去买
depending on Which end of the deal he's doing.
公文包
The briefcases?
金融区?
The financial district?
他们走这边干嘛
What's going on here?
你有什么想法吗
Any idea?
我的大脑正在飞速运转
l'm trying to flush the ideas l have
然而并不知道他们究竟在打什么算盘
'cause none of them seem to fit this.
施工中
Still under construction.
要我把天才奖寄绐你 还是直接亲手献上
Want me to mail or hand deliver your genius aWard?
厉害了
Nice.
真有型
Real stylish.
你要在把头染成基佬发型之前 说这句话?
You're saying this before you use your gay hair shit?
之后就说不出口了
Can't say it after.
要出去探探情况吗?
Time for a Walk by?
到5点45再说
At 5:45.
为什么
Why is that?
他们见面时间最有可能是定在5点半的 考虑到交易中的一方
Well, the nearest most Iikely time for a meet up is 5:30,
可能会出现迟到的情况 我们得把这个时间留出来
and We should alloW the other party room for tardiness.
除非沃格曼迟到了1 9分钟
Unless Vogelmann is 19 minutes Iate.
理论上是可能的 但是实际上不太可能
Possible, but not probable.
我一个人过去打探情况
And l'm doing the Walk by myself.
- 但是一般... - 你人在这儿心不在这儿
- Usua‖y... - You're barely here as it is.
我来承担风险
Any and every bigger risk We come upon is mine to take.
我先帮你弄
I'll do you first.
别搞砸了
Don't make no mess of it.
我之前可是涂鸦老手
l used to graffiti back in the day.
我还记得你的作品有多难看
And l remember What it Iooked like.
你自己什么水平 还好意思说我?
You Would knoW better yourself, you kn0W that?
我也就写写涂鸦字体
IWaS only doing tags.
口口声声说要创作艺术的人可是你
You Was the one trying to make art.
那个声称要画一头斗牛犬 结果被大家以为画的是乌龟的人是谁
Nígga painted a pitbull everybody thought Was a turtle.
没有发现
Nothing.
我们到附近的楼顶上 可能视野会更好些
HoW about getting on a nearby roof for a better vantage?
这样太引人注目了 而且为了防止意外
N0t Worth the exposure,
我们最多只能派一个人去屋顶 这样风险也会更大
or the risk of us getting split up in case things get urgent
这个地方真不合适
This is a bad location for...
那些家伙又是谁
Who the he‖ are those guys?
可能在沃格曼到之前就一直在里面
Must have been here since before Vogelmann arrived.
是他们
lt's them.
谁
Who?
那两个黑人
The black dudes.
跟沃格曼一起上车的那两个
The ones Who drove Vogelmann.
一该死 -妈的
- Anchovies. - Crud.
你知道现在是什么情况吗
Any idea What's going on here?
我不知道 这些人之后肯定有
l dunno. These guys eXpect to be exposed
暴露在人群或者监控器范围内的行动
to people or a camera at some point.
所以他们才会做如此伪装
That's the only Way those disguises make any sense.
他们到底要干什么?
What kind ofjob?
抢劫?
R0bbe「y?
绑架?
Kldnapping?
- 谋杀? - 差不多就这些吧
- Murder? - One or some of those. Yeah.
女士
Ma'am?
你需要帮助吗?
You need some assistance?
抱歉
Sorry.
能帮我按-下吗?
Can you hold that?
请等一下 女士
PIease hold it. Ma'am?
杰佛利
Jeffrey?
杰佛利 让我进去
Jeffrey, let me in.
- 快开门 - 凯莉 别叫了
- Open this. - Kely please Stop ye////7g.
- 我在厕所昵 - 为什么要挂上锁?
- lwas in the bathroom - Why put the chain on the door?
你为什么还没去上班
Why aren Tyou 0n your Way to W0r/(?
你不能用问题来回答我的问题
You are not a‖oWed to ansWer a question With a question.
别跟我喊 好吗 ?
Don 'z' Shout at me okay?
你必须马上下楼
justu You need to go back downsta/m
坐上公交车 然后去上班
get on the bus and go to Work
- 给我开门 - 我做不到
- Open this right noW. - /can't
什么叫你不做不到 你当然做得到
What do you mean you can't? Of course you can.
我真的很想绐你开门 但我不能这么做
/ Want t0, / 唧励 rea/A/ da but / Can 't
你的产假四个星期前就结束 了
The matern/Ty /ea Ve ended four Weeks aga
你为了在这里陪杰克逊
You'Ve used all of your vacation
己经把所有可以请的假都请完 了
and every single sick day staying here With Jackson.
他需要我
He needed me.
我能照顾好他
I'm taking good care of himm
我会在你下班回来之前一直好好照顾他的
and I Will continue to do so until you're home from Work.
我恨你
l hate you.
但我很爱你
And I loVe you tWice as much.
你今天必须要去上班
You need to go to Workm today.
我的工作太蠢了
Myjob is so stupid.
我去到那里
l go there and I se‖
耗费大把青春就为了换取一张工资条
chunks of my life for a paycheck, so thatm
就为了让那些与我素未蒙面的有钱人
rich people l've never even met
把他们的钱存进我从来都没见过的地方
can put money in places l'Ve never even seen.
我心里惦记着自己的宝贝
HoW am l supposed to sit at a stupid desk
你要我怎么去跟别人谈银行账户的事
and talk about bank accounts When my baby is here?
杰克逊还要尿布湿 衣服 还要吃婴儿食品
Jackson needs diapers, and clothes and gourmet baby food.
最终 他还要去上学
Eventually, he's gonna need school supplies.
如果他遗传了我们家牙齿不好的基因
And if he's anything Iike me and my brothers,
他还要带牙套
he'‖ need braces, too.
这些都需要钱 而你比我赚的多得多
NoW, a‖ these things cost money and you make Way more than l do.
我知道
Yeah, l knoW.
所以拜托你赶快上车 去上班吧
Please get on the bus and go to Work.
好
Okay.
对不起 我不该说我恨你
l'm sorry l said l hate you.
没事
That's all right.
我知道你的意思
l knoW What y0u rea‖y meant
我能看看杰克逊吗
Can l see him though?
从门缝里看一眼就行
Just through the opening.
我保证 如果你让我看一眼 我马上就去上班
l promise, l'Il g0 if you Iet me see himjust for a second.
- 我想要摸摸他 - 凯莉 别这样
- I need to touch him. - Kelly, pleasem
就一会儿 我保证 我会走的
I... Just for a second. l sWear l'll go.
你刚刚就是这么保证的 你都没做到
You'Ve broken that sWear before and recently.
你愿意用你儿子的命发誓
Do you sWear on the Iife of our baby
你摸完他之后 真的会马上就走吗?
that you Will Ieave after you've touched him?
不行
No, n0, no.
你必须大声地说出来 这样才算数
Say it out Ioud for it to count, that's hoW sWears Work.
我以我宝贝的生命发誓 我摸完他
l sWear on the Iife of our child that l Will go to Work
我一定马上就去上班
after l've touched him.
你发过誓的
You sWore 0n his life.
下班后再见
l'Il see you both When I get home from Work.
太可爱 了
So Cute.
嘿
-嘿-嗨
- Hey.-Hi.
- 欢迎回来 美女 - 谢谢
- Welcome back, b0n/}'a. - Thank you.
感谢上帝 赞美上帝
Good heavens and praise be to Him.
刚刚从前门走迸来的这个
Can that radiant vision of maternity
浑身闪着母性光辉的人
thatjust Walked through our front doors
真的是我们最亲爱的萨默女士吗?
possibly be our beloved I\/lrs. Summer?
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
欢迎回来 恭喜你
Welcome back and congratulations
将一个如此可爱的男孩降临在这个世界
on bringing such a loVely boy child into this World.
谢谢你 艾德朋顿先生
Thank you, Mn Edmington.
我们银行的所有人都希望你的孩子能健康成长
All of us in the bank have great expectations for your boy.
长大之后能够有所作为
Wondrous expectations on a global scale.
我也是
So do l.
看样子在这一点上 我们达成了共识
Well, in that case, our expectations are alígned.
-是啊-欢迎回来
- Yeah. - Welcome back.
- 见到你很高兴 - 我也是
- Nice to see you. - You too.
萨默小姐 你的缺席让我们甚是想念
l\/lrs. Summen your absence Was a Weight upon us,
你的回归让我们倍感幸运
your return is a divine blessing.
我不就离开了三个月
lt Wasjust three months.
总之 这是一段非常阴郁的时光
Nevertheless, a doleful era.
你生了孩子身材都还保持得这么好
You rea‖y shouldn't Iook that good after having a baby.
谢谢
Thanks.
好让人嫉妒啊
It's kind of annoying hoW good you look.
- 谢谢你 - 我做了纸杯蛋糕
- Thank you. - l made cupcakes.
- 超浓巧克力 - 没错
- Oh, double chocolate. - Of course.
这个照片角 是你丈夫帮我弄的
Oh, yeah, your husband helped me With that part.
谨以此代表我们对宝宝的爱与关切
A sma‖ token, a mínuscule manifestation of our affections.
艾德朋顿先生 还有大家
Mr. Edmington, everybody, rea‖y,
真的太谢谢你们了
thank you for this, rea‖y.
要离开孩子真的很困难 但是
lt Was rea‖y hard to Ieave the baby, butm
今天有安排送钞安排吗?
Any deliveries scheduled for today?
应该没有吧
No, not that l'm aWare of.
所有人听好了
Everyone, listen.
把手举起来 不许动 不然我杀了他
Hands up, and keep them there or this man dies.
把手举起来
Keep your hands raised
乖乖配合我
Coopera te.
如果有人敢乱动 格杀勿论
lfyou make any Sudden mo Ves you W/7/ be executed
如果警察来了 所有人都会没命
/f the police show up evefyone W/// be executed
不要把钱看的比生命还重要
Do not pr/bríz'/2e money over ha Ving a heartbeat
听明白了吗?
Do you under5tand?
明白
Yes.
- 艾德明顿先生 - 是
- Mn Edmíngton - Sir.
后面还有其他员工吗?
Are there any employees in the baC/(?
如果有的话 把他们全部叫出来
/f50, get them r/ght nom
你有20秒的时间
You ha Ve 20 seconds.
后面没有人了 所有人都在前厅了
N0, there is no one in the back, everyone is here in the front.
你确定吗?
Are you certaín of t/7/3 response?
你看起来很心虚
You appear to be uncertain
我很确定所有人
No, l'm quite certain everyone is here
都在前厅了
in the front of the bank.
我们相信你了
We W/7/ accept this response
要是你敢骗我们 我们就摘了你的睾丸
lfyou are m/3z'a/(en, your testícles W/// be removedu
用这把刀
W/T/7 t/7/3.
有话好好说
PIease, let's not talk about anything rash.
如我所说 所有人都在这儿
Everyone is here, as I said,
- 都在银行的前厅了 - 你
- in the front of the bankm - You.
你看起来很诚实也很听话
You Seem honest and 0bed/ènt
把这里的所有人都铐上
Handcuff el/e/j/ 5/hg/e person here
除了经理
except for the managen
用这个
Use these
把他们的手绑在背后
Fasten thek hands behind thefi backs
绑紧点
nght
不要交头接耳
Do not Say anything to anyone at any t/}ne
否则就杀了你
oryou W/// be executed
艾德明顿先生
Mn Edmíngton
是
我会派人跟你去金库
One of us W/// f0//0Wy0u to the l/au/t5.
我要你把它们都打开
Open them aM
我会把所有我能开的金库都打开的
lWill open every vault that I am capable of opening for you.
我们的伙伴没有在
/f our a5s0c/àte does not retum
三分钟之内带着金条回来
with gold bu///bn m three m/}7ute5 or /e$5
我们就杀了这个女的
We W/7/ execute z'/7/3 Woman
北博尔沃克银行有四个持枪劫匪 发绐警察
发送出去
Send it.
能把这个绐我宝宝吗?
Will you make sure my baby gets this?
他叫 杰克逊
His name is Jackson.
他们肯定是往这边跑了
Must have gone this Way.
你觉得他们有发现自己被跟踪了吗?
Think they knoW We're fo‖oWing?
百分之三十的可能
Thirty percent
不过我倒是挺希望他们看见我们 了
Though l'm hoping they saW us at Br0Wnvine.
你希望他们看见我们?
You're hoping they saW us?
是啊 如果他们知道 己暴露了 行动可能就取消了
Yeah, if they knoW they've been spotted, maybe they'll abort
他们正在计划的行动
Whatever it is they got planned.
很高兴听到你改变了计划重心
Glad to hear your priorities changed.
有平民的生命正在遣受威胁 保护他们是永远的重心
We‖, civilians are at risk, they're the priority.
有钱没钱 有警徽没有警徽 你有意见吗?
Money or no money, badge or n0 badge You had doubts?
即使有 也是小到可以忽略的那种
Microscopic ones, if any, butm
不过还是很高兴听到你 能够如此迅速地转移目标
good to hear things articulated.
北堡垒市信托银行
Trusted bank of North BulWark.
找到他们了 那是射击孔吗?
That isn't ambiguous. ls that an embrasure?
- 射击孔是什么? - 看到那个缝隙了吗?
- What's an embrasure? - See that opening?
“安保” 这个词的上面有一条水平的裂缝
The horizontal slit above the Word security.
里面有人
A guy's in there.
他们是来抢劫的
So it's a robbery.
对
Yup.
等他们开车的时候在行动
We Wait until they drive off?
对
Yeah.
我们贸然行动 只会把简单的事情复杂化
It's a robbery until somebody turns it into something Worse.
要不要把他们围堵起来
You Iookíng to boX them in?
没有意义
Pointlessly.
工作日的金融区人太多了
Financial dístrict in a Weekday.
不能在这里和他们发生冲突
Shouldn't engage them here.
你觉得他们干完这票后会回到停车场吗?
You think they'd go back to the parking garage after this?
有百分之五十的可能
Fifty percent.
对于这种是非问题
Fifty percent doesn't value anything.
百分之五十这个答案等于没说
Any yes or no question.
但愿这个家伙不要太过于好奇了
Hope this asshole doesn't get too curious.
银行会在1 5分钟后重新营业 晚点再来吧
"The bank Wi‖ reopen in 15 minutes, come back then.“
他也有可能说50分钟 但是为什么呢?
He might have said 50, but Why?
也可能不是
Probably not.
这家伙是做烟草广告的吗
This guy's Iike a cigarette commerciaL
他们在装货了
They're l0adir1g.
天啊
Christ.
我们本来可以阻止这一切的
We could haVe stopped this.
- 你不想说点什么吗 - 现在不能分心
- Are you gonna say anything? - Focus on that
是我们害死那些人的
We let those people get ki‖ed.
你不应该说点什么吗
You're not gonna say anything?
你不想为我们的失职说点什么吗?
You don't have anything to say about our culpability?
那这个情绪激动的意大利人说的己经够多了
Those ltalian emotions are saying plenty.
- 去死吧 你这个没良心的混蛋 - 我不喜欢感情用事
- Go to he‖, you heartless fuck. - l never saW that opera.
从我们知道这不是一出 常规的毒品交易时开始
Look, by the time We kneW it Wasn't a routine drug deal,
- 一切都晚了 - 你可以上报的啊
- it Was already too late. - You could have ca‖ed it in.
当那辆车离开停车场的时候
When the Van Ieft the parking garage.
你可以向堡垒市警察通报的
Put the BulWark PD on alert.
我们没这么做
We didn't.
在他们到达银行期间只有1 6分钟
The chance of that accomplishing anything
这段时间警局做出有效回应的几率只有50% 甚至25%
in the 16-minute interim, less than 50 percent or even 25.
你可以打电话给堡垒市警察局或者联邦调查局
You Wanna call the BulWark PD, the state police, the Feds,
叫他们来处理这个案子
Iet them handle it, go ahead.
但是那辆货车 还有车上那些混蛋
But that van, and the cut-throats inside,
绝对会在任何执行机构做出回应之前跑的无影无踪
they'll be Vapor before any enforcement agency can respond.
只能靠我们了
We're it.
你们说过除非是自卫
You said you Weren't gonna kill anyone
否则是不会杀死任何人的 你们保证过的
unless it Was in self-defense. You gave us your Word.
上州际公路
Get on the interstate.
你们在银行里办的事纯属多余
lt Was excessive What happened back there.
你是想继续高谈阔论批评我们?
Do you Wish to expand upon your critique?
想给我们上一课不成?
Give us the urban point of vieW?
他没什么想说的了
He ain't got nothing more to say.
别再说了 伙计
Hush that flap, nigga.
好好开车 我们不会有事的
Keep your attention on the road. We'Il get through this.
肌肉男
Muscles,
瘦子
Slim.
在
Yeah.
把你们的枪放进贮物箱里
Place your firearms inside of the glove box.
这是命令
That Wasn't a suggestion.
好的
AIl right.
用报纸把枪遮起来
Cover that Weaponry With the sport section.
把门关上
Close the door.
己经关上 了
lt's closed.
我没听见响声
We didn't hear ít click.
我们要听到关上的响声
We Want to hear it click.
除非有我的允许
Do not open that glove boX
否则绝对不要打开贮物箱
unless I have given you my permissi0n.
知道了
AIl right.
有什么发现吗?
You see something?
没有
Nah, nothing.
该死他们居然上州际公路了
Crud, the interstate.
你觉得他们会去哪儿?
Any idea Where they're gonna land?
肯定是去一个穷乡僻壤的地方 他们要换车
SomeWhere rural, Where they're gonna exchange vehicles,
但是具体会去哪儿呢?
but Where that is...
他们一会儿就得加油了
Need gas pretty soon.
他们也一样
Yeah, so do they.
他们一旦停车 我们就限制住他们
We'Il curb When they pull in someWhere.
车里的汽油桶吗
The cans in the truck?
你刚刚不是问过我这个问题吗?
ls that a question you just asked me?
安静
Quiet.
我想尿尿
I need to pee.
我叫你闭嘴
The other quiet
再敢说一个字我就挖了你的眼睛
Say another Word and you're a pírate.
盖上
Cover that up.
别动
H0ld 5till.
快尿
Squirt.
瘦子
Slim.
什么事
Yeah?
把这个女人尿的尿处理了
Come get rid of this Iady piss.
我们会没事的
We'll get through this.
做好我们自己的事情就行 别管后面的人
Just do What you're paid to do and never mind them back there.
还记得你妈妈带我们出来庆祝你的生日吗?
Remember When your ma brung us out here for your birthday?
咱俩还有至少1 0个当地人
You and me, at Ieast ten other Iocals.
塞维洛也在
Severos Was there too,
虽然当时我们并不想和他玩
even though We aín't rea‖y Want him around.
但是当时还有你姐姐的朋友
But there Was your sister's friends
还有几个邻居
and a couple of neighbors, l think.
你想吃冰淇淋蛋糕 所以你妈妈就用冰柜装了一个来
You Wanted an ice cream cake so your ma brung it in a cooler.
是个什么造型来着?
What Was ít again?
雷克斯霸王龙
Tyrannosaurus reX.
没错
That's right That's right.
我记起来了 你当时可喜欢霸王龙了
l remember noW. Nigga Was a T-rex.
它的牙是用玉米糖做的
And its fangs Was made out of candy corns.
牙身是白色的 尖上还有红色
The ones that Was White With red on the tips
看起来像血一样
that Iook like blood.
还有它正在吃的猎物
The meal he just ate,
应该是剑龙还是什么的
Stegosaurus or Whoever.
我小时候是个恐龙迷啊
IWas rea‖y into dinosaurs back then.
是啊 你特别喜欢
Yeah, you Was.
而且因为你妈妈给了我最大的一块
And you got all pissed and shit
你还生气了好久呢
'cause your ma gave me the biggest piece.
对 我记得
Yeah. Yeah.
寿星就应该吃最大的那块
The birthday boy gets the biggest piece.
这是每个妈妈都该奉行的真理
And that's in the moms' handbook
是啊
Yeah.
但是她可能知道
But she probably kneW my ma
我妈对我不是很好
Wasn't taking care of me too good.
她的确知道
She kneW.
而且我一直暗恋你
AIWays had a crush on you.
她也知道
She kneW that, too.
谢谢你 伙计
Thanks, bro.
咱们能把这个差事做好的
We'll get through this.
同心协力
Togethen
有人跟踪我们吗?
ls anybody fo‖oWing us?
-嗯 有一辆  -没有
- We‖, there's a... - N0.
我们后面只有一辆绿色小卡车和一辆灰色的车
Only things behind us are a green pickup and a gray car
不过离我们还挺远
that got on a Iittle While back.
保持警惕
Be Vigilant.
我知道
AIWayS am.
初步统计有五人死亡
First estimate is five people dead.
2人重伤 1人失踪
TWo in critical, one missing.
他妈的 失踪的那个是人质
Crud. That Iast one's a hostage.
好像两天前刚刚有一大批金条
被送到银行
Was delivered tWo days ago.
这绝对不是个巧合
Not a coincidence.
天哪
Christ.
6条人命画上了句号
Six people got punctuation.
6个人就这么死了
Six human beings died.
我想知道
l gotta kn0W.
如果我们回不来了
ln case We don't come back,
我想知道她会说什么
I gotta knoW What she Would haVe said.
我们会活着回来的
We're coming back.
100%吗?
One hundred percent?
我有80%的概率
l'm at 80.
甚至更高 高到85% 但你只有70%
Maybe even 85, you're 70.
因为你比我有经验?
Experience?
没错 而且我不是意大利人
Yeah, plus l'm not ltalian.
我接通到她的语音信箱了
That's her voicemail.
嘿 德尼斯
Hey, Denise, I...
想请你帮我个忙
l got a favor to ask you.
挺重要的
Pretty important.
我今天晚上要出城
l'mjust out of toWn right noW
但我需要用到家里的一份文件
and l need some information back at my place.
可不可以麻烦你有时间帮我拿一下
So if you could sWíng by and get it,
非常非常感谢你的
I Would rea‖y, really appreciate it.
在我那件褐色夹克的右边口袋里
lt's in the right pocket of my tan blazer,
上次我跟你去见你姐姐时候穿的那件
herringbone one that I Wore to your sister's the Iast time.
我知道这很麻烦
And I knoW this is inconvenient,
但我确实没有其他办法了
but it Would rea‖y be helping me out.
拿到了之后你给我打个电话
Ca‖ me When you get it.
就这样 晚点再说
That's it, l'll talk to you soon.
爱你 再见
Love y0u, bye.
这种求婚方式一点都不浪漫
Ain't the most romantic Way to propose.
我知道
It ísn't.
德尼斯非常聪阴 也很明事理
Denise is smart, she's Very clear-minded.
他不会因为我的求婚方式
She's not gonna change her ansWer one Way or the other
而改变答案的
because of hoW I asked her.
- 我给你 - 别再拿百分比来吓唬我了
- l'd give you aboutm - Don't tell me a percentage.
小心点
Watch this up here.
我看见了
l see it.
这差事干完了 咱们叫个外卖吧
Let's grab take out When We're done With this.
我好想吃粉丝啊
l'm really in the mood for some ce‖ophane noodles.
没问题
Okay.
肌肉男
Muscles.
什么事
Yeah?
后面有人跟踪我们吗?
ls anybody fo‖oWing after us?
那辆绿色小货车和那辆灰色的车呢?
The green pickup, the gray car?
- 没有 - 快看一眼后视镜
- No. - Please check your mirrors.
车后面什么都没有
Nothing but rust and air.
我会注意看的
l'Il keep an eye out.
肌肉男
Musclesm
你在给谁打信号昵?
to Whom are you signaling?
没给谁打信号
Nobody, no one.
我习惯了
ljust did it out of habit
负鼠
Possum.
冰箱 死老鼠
Refrígerator, dead rat.
到了
We here.
我们到了 还是我到了
We are here or We're here.
我是说 我们到了
No, We here.
你能听明白的 对吧
You understood me, didn't you?
- 对吧 - 朝前看
- Didn't you? - Please face forWard.
他可能聋了吧
Figure he's exacerbating.
车库门是关着的?
The garage door is still intact?
应该是
Look like.
打开右面的车库门
Open the right bay.
我能把我的枪拿出来带着么 以防万一
Can l take my gun out the gloVe boX in case?
不能
You may not.
负鼠
Possum.
冰箱
Refrigerator.
死老鼠
Dead rat.
把钥匙绐我
Give me the key.
把给我钥匙
打死他 用备用钥匙
Shoot him and use the spare key.
备用钥匙在我给瘦子的钥匙环上
The spare is on the ring that I gave to Slim.
钥匙昵
Where ís the key?
你去你妈菊花里你找找
Did you check your mother's rectum?
钥匙在哪?
Where ís the key?
去找个直肠大夫吧
Ask a proctologist
坚持住 伙计
Hold tight, nigga.
咱们快走
Hey, get out of here.
别管我 你快走
Just leave me, man. Get out of here.
别说了 伙计
Shut that flap, nigga.
住手 住手 亨瑞
Stop, Stop, Stop, stop, stop. Henry, stopl
见鬼
Damn.
这一切都是我的错 我的馊主意
This Whole thing Was my fault. My idea.
快走
Get.
亨瑞
Henry.
你快跑
You get to go.
给我妈妈买点礼物
Give something to my Ma.
我会照顾好她的
ltake care of her good.
那真是太好了
Yeah.
给她买一台大电视 还有
Get her a nice television. One of thosem
看见钥匙了吗?
Do you see the key?
他吞下去了
He sWa‖oWed it.
瘦子跑了
And Slim's still out there.
我们要不要开到他们前面去 然后在拦住他们的去路
Should We drive past him and come at him from behind?
不 我们要把他们困在这里
No. We need to boX him in right here, right noW.
没有比垃圾场
Conflict couldn't happen in
更适合交火的地点了
a better less populated place than this.
看起来他们跟请的帮手起了矛盾
Looks Iike problems With the hired help.
- 所以里德还活着 - 前门看上去有人把守
- So Reed's still alive? - That front door looks armored.
他们为什么让她来搬尸体?
Why are they making her do that?
他们想在离开前把这里收拾干净
They Wanna clean things up before they go?
- 有75%的概率 - 剩下的25%昵?
- Seventy-five percent - What's the other 25?
我不确定 有不详的预感
l'm not sure. Something Weird.
这也太过分了
This is excessive.
- 咱们车漏油了 - 我知道
- We got a leak. - l'm aWare.
别被击中了
Don't get shot
他们角度不对 打不到我的
They don't have the right angle.
除非他们趴在地上
Unless they get on the ground.
不过我己经就位了 所以主动权在我手上
Since I'm already here, l'Il get off the first shots.
这也是在军队学的?
You Iearn that in the army?
这是几何学
Geometry actua‖y.
你看见另外一个帮手是什么情况吗?
Did you see What happened to that other helper?
- 那个瘦的黑人? - 对
- The skinny black guy? - Him.
没看见
No.
我觉得在第一次交火时就跑了
lthink he disappeared during the first barrage.
又多了一个对我们不利的参数
That's a variable We didn't need.
开始表演吧
Start the party.
没打中吗?
Did you miss?
现在就别挖苦了
Don't be an asshole.
他们的轮胎没有充气
They're rolling bunkers on airless tíres.
把胃切下来
RemoVe the stomach,
保证钥匙别溜进他的肠子里
so that the key doesn't fa‖ into his entrails.
好的
lWi.
是警察吗?
Think they're cops?
要不然也是坏人正在打金条的主意呢
Not unless they're crooked ones, looking for the gold.
我怀疑是瘦子的帮手
l suspect these men are Slim's associates.
专心干你的话
Just stay focused on your Work.
这两个家伙没什么武器 不是我们的对手
This duo isn't properly armed for an engagement With us.
这个是胆囊 看起来像
lt's the pale sac in there, the one that looks Iike...
我知道这是什么
l knoW Which one it is.
小心点儿 别捅到他的肝
Careful not to pop his Iiver.
那玩意奇臭无比 尤其是黑人的
That is the Worst smell in the World, black guys especially.
把它扔下去 开车走人
Let's dump him and drive.
填弹
shell5.
我们应不应该匿名报告警方
Should We call this in, anonymously?
我不太会用这把枪
l'm not equipped for it.
事情越来越奇怪了
Things are getting Weird.
上车
Get in.
- 保护措施 - 那是当然
- Protection? - A hundred percent.
- 怎么不早说 - 快点 系好安全带
- Thanks for Ietting me knoW. - You heard me. Buckle.
她家的地址是拍进去了吗?
ls her home address literally in that picture?
绝对没错 而且她实际上比看起来更年轻
Completely. And she's younger than she looks.
说不定连孩子都有了
She probably had kids.
有没有你亲人住在这个地址里
Do you have any loved ones at this address?
我们会把这张照片发给我们的同伙
That photo had some very unpleasant instructions
他们都是狠角色
that Will go to our associates.
除非你按照我们说的去做 不然你的家人就会有危险
Unless you do exactly What We tell you to do.
汽油漏的越来越凶了
The drip has become a trickle.
我听得到
Yeah. l got ears.
我很担心
I'm concerned.
我们要不要跟他们挑明了
Should We make an announcement?
- 告诉他们我们是警察 - 不行
- Say We're cops? - No.
这样会让人质处境的危险程度
That Wi‖ increase the likelihood of hostage situation
提高60%
by 60 percent
嘿
l,le)/!
蠢货们
Shitheads!
听好了
Listen upl
照我们说的做 你们没有任何谈判的权利
This is the only deal you're gonna get.
我们是为了金条来的
We'rejust here for the gold. That's it.
把金条留在车上 从车里出来
Leave the bu‖ion Where it is and come on out.
我就放你们走
We'‖ let you Walk aWay.
如果你们选择待在车里 我们就杀了所有人
You stay in the van, We'‖ kill a‖ of you,
沃格曼 助手1 号
Vogelmann, sidekick number one,
助手2号 包括那个女孩
sidekick number tWo, the girl, everybody.
把汽油拿来
Get the gas.
催泪弹?
Tea「9a5?
- 什么油? - 汽油
- The gas? - Gasoline.
你们先开会吧 不用等我了 我有事要处理
Don't hold the meeting for me. I've been delayed.
如果我们既要提供无障碍通道
Idon't think the budget is realistic
又要安装金属探测器
for Wheelchair access and metal detectors
那这点预算是显然不够的
so We need to provide them both.
等一下我帮托尼把这事儿搞定了
We‖, let mejust do this thing for Tony
就马上回来 到时候在一起讨论
and then We can get into it When l get back.
谢谢 再见
Thanks. Bye.
给你们45秒的时间从车上出来
You got 45 seconds to come 0ut.
还有1 5秒
You got 15 seconds.
住手
Stopl
看起来像个女的 我不确定
Looks female but Verify.
确实是个女的
She's a she.
里德女士?
Mrs. Reed?
沃格曼先生和他的手下呢?
What happened to Vogelmann and his sidekicks?
你能到车的这边来吗?
Can you get on the other side of this Vehicle?
里德女士 你能听到我说话吗?
I\/lrs. Reed, did you hear me?
我来了
l'm coming.
就是这样 里德女士 做的很棒
Keep coming, Mrs. Reed. You're doing great.
就快到了
You're almost here.
你还好吗?
You okay?
嘿
l一le)/-
住手
Stop.
我不想到伤口
l don't Want t0 see What's under there.
好的
Okay.
那个女的是无辜的
That girl Was innocent
要我带你去急救室吗?
Want me to drive you to the emergency room?
不用了 我己经走不动了
No, it's too much to move.
而且也没有必要了
And there's no reason.
这种情况我都不知道该说什么了
Don't have the right Words for this situation.
天哪 我真的希望这一切
God, l rea‖y hope that thism
错误
mistakem
不会毁了我一世英名
is not What l'm remembered f0r.
我会维护你的名声的
l'Il keep your name out of it.
- 我希望你能 - 我会的
- l hope you can. - l Wi‖.
要我帮你拿吗?
Want me to get that?
她什么时候来的电话
When she ca‖ed?
不知道
ldon't knoW.
那我帮你解锁吧
Well, l'Il type for you.
- 密码是 - 我知道密码是什么
- Passcode is... - I knoW, l knoW What it is.
- 手机给我 - 好
- Let me hold it. - Yeah.
我很遗憾
l'm sorry.
我不想听你说这个
lt Wasn't What l Wanted to hear.
要我帮你把它砸了吗?
Want me to break it?
好
Yeah.
该死
Damnl
满意了吗?
Good?
我投降 金条你拿去吧
l'm surrendering. Taking your deal.
很好 把手举起来 从车里出来
AIl right. Come on out With your hands up.
我需要
l needm
把那个汽油桶放下 老兄
Get rid of that gas can, nigga.
我忙活大半天 可不能无功而返啊
Iain't done a‖ this to see you burn up no money.
金子不是易燃物
Gold isn't flammable.
化了也不行
Yeah, l don't Want it melting.
里面还有钞票昵
And there's cash in there too.
要不你过来亲自解决夫格曼
You Wanna come over here and take care of Vogelmann yourself?
那可不行
No, nigga. No.
你是专业的
You the professionaL
看看你干的这些好事
Look at the all good Work y0u've done here.
居然连一个裸体的女人都不放过
Can execute naked Women and everything.
混蛋
Prick.
不要把钱看得
Do not pr/0r/t/2e money
比自己命还重要
over ha l//}7g a heartbeat
下一发子弹可就不是闹着玩的了
The neXt bullet ain't a Warning.
你穿的防弹衣挺不错的
That bulletproof vest you got there's real nice.
显瘦
Makes you look svelte.
就像女人穿上了塑身衣
Like When a female puts on a girdle.
比你之前那脚踩那个墨西哥人
lt's much more flattering than that Windbreaker
那次穿的风衣好看多 了
you Wore on the neWs When you stomped that Mexican.
你是在哪发现我的?
Where did you spot me?
你们从银行开始跟着我们的时候
When you droVe by the bank.
还有在林园大道上跟踪我们的时候
And tWice When you Was folloWing on the parkWay.
你想干什么?
What d0 you Want?
呆在那儿别动
Stay right there.
我想当面谢谢你
So l can thank you face to face
谢谢你帮我把那些冷血的垃圾清理了
for Wiping out a‖ these cruel-ass thugs.
被停职的警察难道都好这一 口
That's What most cops do When they get suspended.
劫抢这些银行抢劫犯
Go rob bank robbers.
你脱了干什么?
Why you taking that off?
我要用皮带止血
l need the strap to stop the bleeding.
好吧
'Aight.
我有问题要问你
I'm gonna ask y0u some questions.
你要是敢不说实话
You tell me some bullshit
我就把你杀死那个白人女孩的录像
and l send that Video l made
寄绐媒体新闻那些人
of you killing that White girl t0 the neWs.
我拍摄时选取的角度可是很专业的
l got a real good angle from up there.
你取下面具的画面我都拍到了
Even got you When you took off your mask.
- 问吧 - 堡垒市警察局如果知道
- So ask. - What do the Bulwark PD knowm
- 厉害啊 - 彼此彼此
- Nigga. - LikeWise.
咱们有话直说吧
Let's talk through this.
有话直说
Make some Words.
我们应该把这个地方收拾干净然后把金子分了
We should clean up this mess together and split the gold.
我们也可以继续斗下去
We can fight each other some more,
直到两败俱伤 但是我们也可以双赢
do this until We're crippled or dead, or We can both be rich.
我觉得这个选择题不难做
ldon't see hoW this is a dilemma.
你让我相信一个誓察
Trusting a c0p,
一个作风如此不正的警察 还不好选择吗?
one that's crooked as fuck, is the dilemma.
我对你只有一件事情非常肯定
Only thing absolutely certain about y0u
那就是你对干入职宣言上的内容根本不在平
is that you don't gíve a shit about any oath you sWear to.
我女几两天前又被人骚扰了 已经是第五次了
My daughter got assaulted for the fifth time tWo days ago.
我妻子有严重的多发性硬化症
l\/ly Wife has multiple sclerosis and can't even Walk
不拄拐都走不了
half the time Wíthout a cane.
我需要这笔钱
l need this.
- 73分 - 64分
- Seventy-thirty. - SiXty-forty.
成交
'Aight.
车库里有备用车?
There's a getaWay car in there?
警宫真精明
Detective is astute.
我们得把这个扔到湖里沉了
We need to toW this one to the lake.
好吧
AIl right.
咱们一起慢慢的卸掉枪里所有的子弹
Let's unload the guns together and sloWIy
谁都别动歪脑筋
so neither one of us is tempted.
好的
AIl right.
那我们的朋友怎么办?
What We do With our friends?
不能把他们留在这儿
Can't Ieave them here.
但也不能把他们带回去
We can't go bringing them back With us neither
这样会暴露我们的
Without exposing ourselves.
把他们埋了吧
We bury them.
我都不知道他们会抓个女的当人质
ldidn't knoW they Was gonna grab no Woman.
也没有人应该被枪杀 除非那个人先用枪指着我们
Nobody Was supposed to get shot unless they pu‖ed a gun on us.
这是我们说好了的
That Was the deal.
你真的相信他们的鬼话 还是只是自欺欺人而己?
Did you believe that or did you just Want to?
这几没有枪
Ain't no guns in here.
那辆货车里有很多枪
A lot of firearms in that Van.
咱们说好了64分
Our Word's good. lt'Il be 60/40.
咱们一起去那辆货车
We go in the van at the same time.
随便吧 反正都是手到擒来的事情
Whatever you Want lt's a‖ cotton candy.
那里面的味道不会好闻
lt's not gonna smell great in there.
我们把金子放在这
We'‖ put the gold in here.
为什么 这个车已经面目全非了
Why? This Wreck is dead as an insect.
我知道 但我得坐在这车上驾驶
Right, but l got to sit in it and steer.
如果把东西都放在你车上
l don't Want you cutting me loose
那你突然变卦 带着东西逃之夭夭怎么办?
and driving off With everything in your trunk.
你太能妄想了 疑心太重了
You're so paranoid and suspicious
害的我都有点疑心病了
you're making me paranoid and suspicious.
我只是怕你骗我而己
l'm just trying to avoid temptation.
警官看来还是个神职人员啊
Detective is a priest.
动作慢点
We go sloW.
用得着这么担心吗
lt's a‖ cotton candy.
这味道就像诏气池炸了一样
Sme‖s like a‖ these dudes shitted themselves.
不要碰
Don't fondle any guns.
过父亲节的时候
On Father's Day,
你女几会给你敬一个礼还是两个?
does your daughter give you one salute or tWo?
她很尊重我的
She's respectfuL
都在这些包里
lt's all in these duffels.
对
Yeah.
有几块掉了
Some Ioose bits on the concrete.
我来把这个解开
l'Il unhook these.
我去拿包
l'll get the bags.
抱歉
Sorry.
记得避开那摊淤泥
Don't driVe too close to that muck.
你确定你不是小学老师吗?
You sure you ain't an elementary teacher,
你是不是习惯了和那些啥都不懂的小屁孩打交道的那种
used to dealing With Iittle kids Who don't know nothing?
我要说的应该是“什么都不知道吧”
l believe What you meant to say Was, "Who don't knoW anythíng."
你懂我意思 对吗
You understood me, didn't you?
是 但是你说的话会看起来智商不太高
Yeah, but you're a lot smarter than you sound,
事实上 你是个很聪明的人
a Whole lot smarter from What l'Ve seen.
被低估是件好事儿
lt's good to be underestimated.
你这么做是为了防止我以为我自己
You're doing that in case I confuse
- 开的是一艘潜水艇? - 没错
- this car With a submarine? - Yup.
别激动
Keep calm.
- 你搞什么 - 只是个预防措施
- What the fuck is this shit? - Just a precautionary measure.
我不想伤害你 把你的手机拿出来
l don't intend t0 hurt you. Take out your cell phone.
那段录像是我的保险单
That video is my insurance policy.
错了 如果他们让你去坐牢你能指认我
Wrong. You can identify me if they toss you injail.
相反 我也可以指认你 我们两个本身
lf We get brought to tral, l can do the same to you.
就能让对方保持沉默 这才是最公平的做法
We keep each other quiet. That's fair. That's balanced.
但是那段录像加大了我受到你勒索的风险
But that video opens me up to extortion from you,
不止是你 所有收到你视频的人或者
or anyone you send it to, or for anyone that hacks
-黑客破解了你的手机他们都可以要挟我 - 不会发生这种事的
- into your hardWare. - None of that's gonna happen.
咱们 64分
We 60/40.
我只是在排除不稳定的因素
l'm just trying to remove temptation.
把枪放下
Get that gun off my neck.
把手机给我 密码告诉我
Give me your phone and give me your passWord.
把枪拿开
Get that fucking gun off me.
我不想伤害你 但是
Idon't Wanna hurt you but if...
你就是个笨蛋
You fucking dumbass.
我根本就不会要挟你的
lwasn't gonna blackmail you.
我是言而有信的人
I\/ly Word is good.
你应该相信我的
You should haVe trusted a nigga.
我长这么大 做过的坏事也就偷了几辆车
All I ever did for this Was steal some autos,
磕了几回毒品
peddle some bloW
把那个弄残我兄弟 的家伙送进加护病房而己
and put the fool Who crippled my brother into intensive.
我都没杀过人
l ain't never killed nobody.
见鬼
Damn.
好好安葬我朋友
Bury my friend, please.
我不想让他也牵扯进来
l don't Want him involved in this.
- 好的 一谢谢
- All right. - Thanks.
从你开始说你的女儿被人欺负
You Was being true and honest When you said that shit
你妻子得了重病的事
about your baby girl getting attacked
都是真的吗?
and your Wife With her mess?
我说的都是真的
l Was being honest
那好 我会分一点给他们
AIl right. l'Il give them some.
40%
Forty percent
她们拿不到那么多
They ain't getting 40.
但是我会好好照顾她们的
But l'll take good care of them.
抱歉 只能把你们埋在这了 警官们
Sorry to put you into these, cops,
但是现在就先将就一下吧
but l can't be finicky right noW.
等这一切结束 过了风头之后
After a‖ this is finished, forgotten,
我会回来再好好安葬你们
I'Il come back and bury you right.
11个月后
嘿亨利
Hey, Henry.
如果你介意的话 我可以让克里斯托弗进客房
Oh, I could have Christopher finish this in the guest room
- 帮我按摩 - 没关系 妈妈
- íf you Want. - No problem, Ma.
我知道你按摩的时候喜欢看着大海
l knoW you like to look at the ocean When you get massaged.
对
Yes.
哦 对了 你出去的这段时间 邮箱里多了很多封邮件
Oh, you had some stuff come in the mail While you Were gone.
应该是你的经纪人
lthink it Was your broker.
等下再说 我看了好几个小时的数字了 头都大了
Been up too many hours t0 look at numbers right noW.
伊森在家还是在杰端米家?
Ethan's home or at 」eremy's?
他在游戏室里
He's in the game room.
知道了
AIl right.
晚饭吃寿司可以吗?
You Want sushi for dinner?
你想吃的话 我可以给你做一些家常菜
l'll make you something homemade if you Want.
谢谢
Thanks.
你做的菜我当然愿意吃
IWould enjoy your cooking.
游玩的怎么样?
Your game good?
你都忙完了吗?
You done With everything?
忙完了
Fina‖y.
星期四晚于东南部堡垒市发生的
The Victíms of the home in Va5/bn
- 起入室抢劫的遇难者
that occurred /n S0ut/7-ea$t Bu/War/( Thursday n/ght..
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, sWeetie.
- 楼下有个包裹 - 请把门关上
- There's a package downstairsm - Close the door, please.
到目前为止 这场暴力事件
No Suspect for thís Violent crime
相关嫌疑人还未被抓获
has been apprehended at this t/}77e.
警方负责人也未承认
The police c0mm/3S/0ner has ne/'z'/7er c0nfi沂me0{"
我觉得是爸爸寄来的
lthink it's from Dad.
寄件人地址写的什么?
What does the return address say?
瑞支曼 和他的办公室地址
lt says Rídgeman and a PO Box.
给我吧
Let me have it, please.
天哪 好重啊
Oh, God. This is heavy.
- 我可以帮你打开 - 不用
- I can help you open it. - Uh, no, no.
这是给我的 我自己来 我想一个人打开它
It's addressed to me, and I Want to open ít myself, in private.
- 可是妈妈 我也想... - 萨拉 拜托
- Mom, I Wannam - Sara, please.
好吧
Okay.
我今天晚上没法做饭 所以我点了中餐
IWasn't able to cook tonight so I ordered Chinese.
- 好的 一亲一下
- Okay. - Kiss.
谢谢
Thank you.
暂停一下
Pause this.
我出去寄包裹的时候
When l Was out mailing that package,
突然想到在我们的生活
l start thinking about that game
发生翻天覆地的改变之前 我们在玩的那一款游戏
We Was playing right before everything changed for us,
在丛林里的那个游戏
the one in thejungle.
你还有吗
You still got it?
《 丛林狩猎 》
Shotgun 5afar/?
当然
Yeah.
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
好了
Yeah.
开始猎杀狮子吧
Let's hunt some Iions.